What are the biggest things you've
learned? What are the biggest things
you've learned? What are the tips for
other content creators?
>> I think definitely figuring out what
your sort of [music] I guess unfair
advantages or like unique interests are
and learning more about yourself. I
think making content is like
honestly a good sort of [music]
self-discovery vehicle. Yeah. Um because
through making these like YouTube videos
especially there's so much work to make.
You'll quickly learn like what you
[music] actually enjoy talking about,
what you enjoy you know making videos
about and what you
you don't and so you [music] can kind of
use it as a way to learn more about
yourself. But I think that is important
[music] for long-term success since like
YouTube in particular is not like a
I mean you can go viral quickly but most
people like it takes a lot of videos,
years to really [music] pop off and so
you figuring out how to you know be in
it for the long term.